Sewall Wright Papers 1895-1988 Mss.Ms.Coll.60
American Philosophical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1895-1988; 13.5 Linear feet
  - Eaten, Robert M., 1952 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ecology, 1951 (Box Series I-8)
    Deevey, Edward S., Jr.
  - The Econometric Society, 1979 (Box Series I-8)
    Gordon, Julie P.
  - Edgerton, Harold A., 1935-36 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edington, Marjorie, 1953 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edgren, Richard A., 1952 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edward, A. G., 1961 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edward, J. Gordon, 1954 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edwards, J. W., 1950 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edwards, Jean A.H., 1957 (Box Series I-8)
  - Edwards, Toni, 1963 (Box Series I-8)
  - Efron, Robert, 1968 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ehrlich, Paul R., 1963 (Box Series I-8)
  - Eighth International Congress of Genetics, 1947 (Box Series I-8)
    Bonnier, G.
  - Eisen, Eugene, 1964 (Box Series I-8)
  - Eisenhart, C., 1938 (Box Series I-8)
  - Eisenhart, Churchill, 1976 (Box Series I-8)
  - Eisenharte, 1951 (Box Series I-8)
  - Elandt-Johnson, Regina, 1970 (Box Series I-8)
  - Eleventh International Congress of Genetics, 1962 (Box Series I-8)
    Geerts, S. J.
  - Elias, M.K., 1946-47 (Box Series I-8)
  - Eliot, Thomas D., 1966 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ellinger, Tage U., 1922-24 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ellman, Leonard, 1970 (Box Series I-8)
  - Elston, Robert C., 1967 (Box Series I-8)
  - Elton, Charles, 1945 (Box Series I-8)
  - Emergency Committee of Atomic Scientists, 1947 (Box Series I-8)
    Schaffner, Joseph Halle; Einstein, Albert
  - Emerson, Alfred, 1935-61 (Box Series I-8)
  - Emerson, R. A. (Rollins Adams), 1939; 2.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-8)
    Biographical and personal data -- Muller, Hermann Joseph; Displaced German scholars; Muller, Hermann Joseph; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Emerson, Sterling, 1947-57 (Box Series I-8)
  - Emlen, John T. Jr., 1948 (Box Series I-8)
  - Endler, John A., 1978 (Box Series I-8)
  - Ephrussi, Boris, 1936-1946; 6.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-8)
    Drosophila genetics; Publication -- American Naturalist; Requests for reprints; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
  - Epling, Carl, 1943-59 (Box Series I-8)
  - [Epling], Ruth, n.d. (Box Series I-8)
  - Erickson, Ralph O., 1945-58 (Box Series I-8)
  - Eshel, Ilan, 1972-73 (Box Series I-8)
  - Espindola, Gualberto C., 1978 (Box Series I-8)
  - Etherington, I.M.H., 1943 (Box Series I-8)
  - Etkin, William, 1938 (Box Series I-8)
  - Europa Pulbications Limited, 1950 (Box Series I-8)
  - Evolution (Box Series I-8)
    - Amadon, Dean, 1951 (Box Series I-8)
    - Colbert, Edwin, 1951-52 (Box Series I-8)
    - Erhart, G, W., 1951 (Box Series I-8)
    - Johnson, Ralph G., 1966-68 (Box Series I-8)
    - Jones, J. Knox Jr., 1965 (Box Series I-8)
    - Lerner, Howard, 1959-61 (Box Series I-8)
    - Mayr, Ernst, 1948-50 (Box Series I-8)
    - Michener, Charles D., 1963-64 (Box Series I-8)
    - Mos imann, James E., 1957 (Box Series I-8)
    - Olson, Everett C., 1953-58 (Box Series I-8)
    - Schaeffer, Bobb, 1952 (Box Series I-8)
  - Experimental Zoology, 1945-46 (Box Series I-8)
    Harrison, Ross G.
  - Fairchild, David, 1920-43 (Box Series I-8)
    Kennan, George
  - Falconer, Douglas S., 1954-77 (Box Series I-8)
  - Farkas, Himsley, 1961 (Box Series I-8)
  - Farias, Antonio, 1924 (Box Series I-8)
  - Fau de Casajuana, R., 1973 (Box Series I-8)
  - Faxon' s, 1950 (Box Series I-8)
  - Federation of American Societies for Experimental Biology, 1961-78 (Box Series I-8)
    Altman, Philip L.
  - Feldman, Gabriel E., 1966-77 (Box Series I-9)
  - Feller, W., 1952-66 (Box Series I-9)
  - Felsenstein, Joseph, 1974-80 (Box Series I-9)
  - Ferguson, Glenn W., 1974 (Box Series I-9)
  - Ferrari, 1964 (Box Series I-9)
  - Festing, Michael, 1972-76 (Box Series I-9)
  - Finch, Durell M., 1923 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fingerman, Milton, 1951 (Box Series I-9)
  - Finney, D.J., 1944 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fischer, C.H., 1950 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fish, H.D., 1924 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fisher, R. A. (Ronald Aylmer), 1931-1950; 10.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-9)
    Drosophila genetics; Evolution; Fellowships, assistantships; Glass, Bentley; Haldane, John Burdon Sanderson; Population genetics; Publication -- Genetics; Publication -- Journal of Heredity; Reviews; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Teaching; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements
  - Fix, Evelyn, 1954 (Box Series I-9)
  - Flory, Walter S., 1931-55 (Box Series I-9)
  - Ford, C.E., 1947 (Box Series I-9)
  - The Foreign Service of the United States of America, 1949 (Box Series I-9)
    O'Sheel, Patrick
  - Forkner, Claude E., 1951 (Box Series I-9)
  - Foster, Helen, 1924 (Box Series I-9)
  - Foster, Morris, 1952-56 (Box Series I-9)
  - Foster, R.H.K., 1933 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fox, Allen S., 1949-52 (Box Series I-9)
  - Frank, Peter W., 1956-1957 (Box Series I-9)
  - Franke, Donald E., 1977 (Box Series I-9)
  - Franke, Kurt W., 1934 (Box Series I-9)
  - Frankham, R., 1976-77 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fraser, A.S., 1951-70 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fraser, Joan, 1975 (Box Series I-9)
  - Freeman, S.C., 1920 (Box Series I-9)
  - Freeman, W.H. and Co., 1969 (Box Series I-9)
  - Freire-Maia, Newton, 1957 (Box Series I-9)
  - Frisch, Ragnar, 1947 (Box Series I-9)
  - Frolik, E.F., 1949 (Box Series I-9)
  - Frydenberg, Ove, 1956 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fryer, H.C., 1939-46 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fryer, J.R., 1936 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fulker, David, 1974 (Box Series I-9)
  - Fuller, John L., 1973 (Box Series I-9)
    Behavioral Genetics Association
  - Futuyma, Douglas T., 1979 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gaines, W.L., 1931 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gamble, J.A., 1925 (Box Series I-9)
  - Garber, E.D., 1935 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gardner, G. Peabody Jr., 1936 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gardner, H.A., 1931-32 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gardner, R, Nelson, 1933 (Box Series I-9)
  - Garnett, Eugene H., 1931 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gasser, Herbert S., 1943 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gates, R.R., 1952 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gates, William H., 1931-45 (Box Series I-9)
  - Gause, G.F., 1937 (Box Series I-9)
  - Geiringer, Hilda, 1947-48 (Box Series I-9)
    Mrs, R. von Mises
  - Geisler, Murray A., 1963 (Box Series I-9)
  - The Genetical Society, 1949-51 (Box Series I-9)
    Pontecorvo, G.; Brown, R.; Fincham, J.R.S.
  - Genetics, 1931-1972; 24 folders (Box Series I-9)
    Business; Caspari, Ernst Wilhelm; Crow, James F.; Dobzhansky, Theodosius; Drosophila genetics; Dunn, Leslie Clarence; Editorial matters; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Genetics of plants; Haldane, John Burdon Sanderson; History of biology, especially genetics; Lewontin, Richard Charles; Mendel, Gregor; Population genetics; Publication -- Genetics; Referee's report; Sonneborn, Tracy M.; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Stern, Curt; Sturtevant, Alfred Henry
    - Genetics, 1943-52 (Box Series I-9)
    - Avery, George S., Jr., 1949-50 (Box Series I-9)
    - Bacon, Alice M., 1943 (Box Series I-9)
    - Booth, G.E., 1933-34 (Box Series I-9)
    - Brehme, K. S., 1937 (Box Series I-9)
    - Brink, R. A., 1952-54 (Box Series I-9)
    - Caspari, Ernst W., 1967-70 (Box Series I-9)
    - Crow, James F., 1951-54 (Box Series I-9)
    - Dunn, L.C., 1935-38 (Box Series I-9)
    - Gilbertson, Edna, 1962 (Box Series I-9)
    - Gregory, P.W., 1946-47 (Box Series I-9)
    - Haldane, J.B.S., 1934 (Box Series I-9)
    - Irwin, M.R., 1947 (Box Series I-9)
    - Jones, D.F., 1934 (Box Series I-9)
    - Latter, Barrie, 1970 (Box Series I-9)
    - Lewontin, R.C., 1970 (Box Series I-9)
    - Miller, C. R., 1931-32 (Box Series I-9)
    - Oliver, Clarence P., 1957-62 (Box Series I-9)
      Chai, C.K.; Castle, Dr. .[Wm.]
    - Perkins, David D., 1962-67 (Box Series I-9)
    - Prout, Timothy, 1972 (Box Series I-9)
    - Rhoads, M.M., 1940-46 (Box Series I-9)
    - Sonneborn, T.M., 1948 (Box Series I-9)
    - Stern, Curt, 1946-52 (Box Series I-9)
    - Sturtevant, A.H., 1934 (Box Series I-9)
  - Genetics and Biometric Laboratory, Government of Orissa, India, 1964 (Box Series I-10)
    Whitby, Pauline
  - Genetics Discussion Group, n. d. (Box Series I-10)
  - Genetics Society of America, 1931-1950; 22 folders (Box Series I-10)
    Business; Committee activities; Conferences and symposia; Demerec, Milislav; Displaced German scholars; Dunn, Leslie Clarence; Emerson, Rollins Adams; Genetics Society of America; Stadler, Lewis John; Sturtevant, Alfred Henry; Whiting, Phineas W.
    - Atwood, Sanford, 1950 (Box Series I-10)
    - Bliss, C.I., 1944 (Box Series I-10)
    - Demerec, M., 1935-36 (Box Series I-10)
    - Emerson, R. A., 1931 (Box Series I-10)
    - Gates, Wm. H., 1934 (Box Series I-10)
    - Horowitz, N.H., 1975 (Box Series I-10)
    - Irwin, Bob (Box Series I-10)
    - Jones, D. F., 1934 (Box Series I-10)
    - Lewis, E.B., 1962 (Box Series I-10)
    - Metz, Charles W., 1947 (Box Series I-10)
    - Muller, H. J., 1947 (Box Series I-10)
    - Painter, T. S., 1937 (Box Series I-10)
    - Richy, F. D., 1937 (Box Series I-10)
    - Russell, Elizabeth, 1975 (Box Series I-10)
    - Russell, W. L., 1961 (Box Series I-10)
    - Scott, Paul, 1935 (Box Series I-10)
    - Singleton, W. R., 1951 (Box Series I-10)
    - Smithies, Oliver, 1975 (Box Series I-10)
    - Snyder, 1944 (Box Series I-10)
    - Stadler, L. J., 1931-33 (Box Series I-10)
    - Sturtevant, 1944 (Box Series I-10)
    - Thompson, David H., 1947 (Box Series I-10)
    - Whiting, P.W., 1931-34 (Box Series I-10)
  - Genetics Society of Canada, 1962 (Box Series I-10)
    Johnson, A. S.
  - George, Adda Gentry, 1945 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gerard, R.W., 1940-56 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gerritsen, Neal, 1951 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gersh, Eileen Sutton, 1948 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gerwould, J.H., 1944 (Box Series I-10)
  - Giles, Norman H., 1981 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gilfillan, S.C., 1944-72 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gill, Douglas E., 1977 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gingrich, Wendell, 1934 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gini, Corrado, 1931-46 (Box Series I-10)
  - Ginsberg, Benson, 1946-77 (Box Series I-10)
  - Giuliani, Renzo, 1949 (Box Series I-10)
  - Glaser, R.W., 1921 (Box Series I-10)
  - Glass, Bentley, 1950-1955; 7.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-10)
    Evolution -- Race; Human genetics; Population genetics; Publication -- American Naturalist; Sheppard, Philip M.; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
  - Goddijn, W.A., 1931-32 (Box Series I-10)
  - Godfrey, George F., 1968 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goethe, C.M., 1943-50 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goldberg, Arthur S., 1971-77 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goldberg, Samuel, 1948 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goldschmidt, R. (Richard Benedict), 1922-1951; 7.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-10)
    Fellowships, assistantships; Invitations; Lectures, public speaking -- University of California, Berkeley; Population genetics
  - Goldstein, Albert, 1943 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gonzalez Diaz de Garayo, Concha, 1974 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gooch, Marjorie, 1931 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goodale, H. D. (Hubert Dana), 1932-1947; 6.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-10)
    Genetics -- Cattle; International Congress of Genetics; Population genetics; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics
  - Goodell, C.J., 1944-47 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goodman, Morris, 1981 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gordon, Cecil, 1949 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gordon, F. B., 1945 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gordon, Myron, 1933-52 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gordon, Robert Dean, 1947 (Box Series I-10)
  - Goudge, T.A., 1954 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gould, Stephen Jay, 1981 (Box Series I-10)
  - Govindan, P., 1948 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gow, R. M., 1924 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gowen, John W., 1924-52 (Box Series I-10)
  - Graham, Margaret A., 1934 (Box Series I-10)
  - Grant, Verne, 1980 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gray, J., 1950 (Box Series I-10)
  - Gray, Peter, 1960 (Box Series I-10)
  - Grea, Earl, 1941 (Box Series I-10)
  - Greb, M.T., 1960 (Box Series I-10)
  - Green, C.V., 1932-34 (Box Series I-10)
  - Green, Earl and Margaret, 1966 (Box Series I-10)
  - Green, M.M., 1971 (Box Series I-10)
  - Green, W.W., 1949-53 (Box Series I-10)
  - Green, Wyman R., 1957 (Box Series I-10)
  - Greenwood, A.W., 1949 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gregg, Thomas G., 1969 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gregory, R.W., 1932-53 (Box Series I-11)
  - Grell, E.H., 1963 (Box Series I-11)
  - Grene, Marjorie, 1965 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gries, Wanda, 1977 (Box Series I-11)
  - Griffen, A.B., 1948-51 (Box Series I-11)
  - Griffing, Bruce, 1949 (Box Series I-11)
  - Griggs, Robert F., 1946 (Box Series I-11)
  - Growth, 1941-47 (Box Series I-11)
    Reimann, Stanley P.; Rahn, Otto
  - Gruenwald, Peter, 1943 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gruhlke, R.C., 1920 (Box Series I-11)
  - Grüneberg, H., 1943-67 (Box Series I-11)
  - Guggenheim, John Simon Memorial Foundation, 1930 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gurian, Joan, 1949 (Box Series I-11)
  - Gurland, John, 1963 (Box Series I-11)
  - Guthrie, R., 1944 (Box Series I-11)
  - Guttman, Ruth and Louis, 1964 (Box Series I-11)
  - Györffy, Barna, 1957 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hadorn, Ernst, 1937 (Box Series I-11)
  - Haidemenkis, E.D., 1970 (Box Series I-11)
    International Science Foundation
  - Haines, George, 1923-31 (Box Series I-11)
  - Haldane, J. B. S. (John Burdon Sanderson), 1919-1968; 23.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-11)
    Beadle, George Wells; Bibliographical matters; Biographical and personal data; Conferences and symposia; Congratulations, greetings, thanks -- National Academy of Sciences; Dronamraju, Krishna R.; Drosophila genetics; Evolution; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Honors -- Kimber Award; Honors -- Royal Society (Great Britain); Mouse genetics; Physiology; Population genetics; Rabbit genetics; Recommendations; Sonneborn, Tracy M.; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.; World War II -- England
  - Hale, Fred, 1934-35 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hall, Claude H., 1957 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hall, E. Raymond, 1943-48 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hall, Fred J., 1924 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hall, J. K., 1924 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hall, Marion T., 1953 (Box Series I-11)
  - Halstead, 1954 (Box Series I-11)
  - [Hamburger], 1934 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hamilton, Bengt, 1933-54 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hamilton, James B., 1943 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hammond, John, 1949-1950 (Box Series I-11)
    Dunn, H. H.
  - Hammond, P. H., 1922 (Box Series I-11)
  - The Handbook of Biological Data, 1949 (Box Series I-11)
    The Committee on the Handbook of Biological Data; Panel of Appraisers
  - Hannah, Pauline, 1975 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hanovitz, William, 1942-53 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hanson, Frank Blair, 1933-44 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hanson, Karl B., 1931 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hanson, Martin (Box Series I-11)
  - Hanson, W.D., 1962 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hardenborgh, W.S., 1942 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hardin, Garrett, 1946 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hardy, Alister C., 1949-63 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hardy, C.W., 1923 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hargitt, George T., 1932 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harris, Dewey L., 1964 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harris, Henry, 1969-70 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harris, J. Arthur, 1926 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harris, J.F., n.d. (Box Series I-11)
  - Harris, Reginald, 1934 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harris, Theodore E., 1964 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harrison, G. Ainsworth, 1980 (Box Series I-11)
    Lord Bullock' s Dictionary of Modern Thought
  - Harrison, R. Wendell, 1948 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harrison, Boss G., 1931-1946 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hartl, Daniel L., 1978-80 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hartley, Carl, 1920 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hartman, Carl G., 1943-54 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hartshorne, Charles, 1963 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harvard University (Box Series I-11)
    - Bussey Institute for Research in Applied Biology, 1924 (Box Series I-11)
      Foster, Helen Louise
    - Conant, James B., 1935-52 (Box Series I-11)
    - Doty, Paul, 1957 (Box Series I-11)
      Chemistry Department
    - East, E., 1935 (Box Series I-11)
    - Honorary Degree, 1951 (Box Series I-11)
    - Redfield, A., 1935 (Box Series I-11)
    - Rome, A., 1935 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hasler, Arthur D., 1956 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hathaway, Harry E., 1942 (Box Series I-11)
  - Harvey, James S., 1953 (Box Series I-11)
  - Haverstock, G.L., 1933-35 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hayes, H.K., 1931-32 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hays, F.A., 1944-45 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hays, Leonard, 1924 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hayward, H., 1924 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hazel, L.N., 1947 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hegg, G., 1959 (Box Series I-11)
  - Heidenthal, Gertrude, 1934-1958; 29.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-11)
    Biographical and personal data; Cytogenetics; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Genetics -- Wasps; International Congress of Genetics; International Congress of Zoology; Laboratory techniques, equipment; Lectures, public speaking; Marine Biological Laboratory, Woods Hole; Radiation genetics; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Teaching; Travel -- Invitations, arrangements; Whiting, Phineas W.; World War II -- Impact on science
  - Heikertinger, Franz, 1933 (Box Series I-11)
  - Helm, Exra, 1922 (Box Series I-11)
  - Hellbaum, A.A., 1943-44 (Box Series I-11)
  - Helquist, Christie M., 1978 (Box Series I-11)
    Turner, John R. C.
  - Hemens, Rollin D., 1945 (Box Series I-11)
  - Herb, R.G., 1961 (Box Series I-11)
  - Herluf, 1949 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hermann and Cie., 1939-40 (Box Series I-12)
    Hermann, E. R.
  - Herndon, C. Nash, 1944 (Box Series I-12)
  - Herskowitz, Irwin, 1958-73 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hesler, L.R., 1945 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hess, Walter M., 1949 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hickey, Charles D., 1957-58 (Box Series I-12)
  - Highton, Richard, 1966-74 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hile, Ralph, 1940 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hill, Bert, 1951 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hiraizumi, Y., 1972 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hirschfelder, J.O., 1949 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hisaw, Frederick L., 1947 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hitt, Holly, 1973 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hoadley, Leigh, 1937 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hedge, Robert W., 1966 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hoenigsberg, H.F., 1968 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holden, Sally, 1971 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hollaender, Alexander, 1948-1960; 31.0 Item(s) (Box Series I-12)
    Biochemistry and organic chemistry; Conferences and symposia; Cytogenetics; Embryology, developmental genetics; Genetics -- Guinea pigs; Invitations; Oak Ridge National Laboratory; Population genetics; Radiation genetics; Statistics, biostatistics, biometrics; Unpublished manuscripts, notes, etc.
  - Holmes, R.H., 1950 (Box Series I-12)
  - Holzinger, Karl J., 1933 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hooker, Davenport, 1954 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hopkins, Carl E., 1964 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hopps, H.C., 1941 (Box Series I-12)
  - Horlacher, W.R., 1924 (Box Series I-12)
  - Horowitz, N. H., 1944-45 (Box Series I-12)
  - Horowitz, Samuel B., 1956 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hornung, P., 1963 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hotelling, Harold, 1945 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hough, L.F., 1948 (Box Series I-12)
  - Houghton, F.L., 1924 (Box Series I-12)
  - Houghton Mifflin Co., 1978 (Box Series I-12)
    Reid, Anne A.
  - House Un-American Activities Committee (Box Series I-12)
    - Board of Health, Chicago, 1965 (Box Series I-12)
    - Chicago Daily News, May 29, 1965 (Box Series I-12)
    - Chicago Sun Times, 1965 (Box Series I-12)
    - Committee for Preserving Constitutional Rights, 1965 (Box Series I-12)
    - Congressional Record, House (Feb. 25):3562-4, [1965] (Box Series I-12)
    - Dillard, Irving (Chicago American), 1965 (Box Series I-12)
    - Hall, Yolanda F., [1965] (Box Series I-12)
    - Harrington, Michael (New York Herald Tribune ), 1965 (Box Series I-12)
    - Jenner, Albert E. Jr., 1965 (Box Series I-12)
    - Kupcinet (Chicago Sun Times ), 1965 (Box Series I-12)
    - Llorens, David (Woodlawn Booster), 1965 (Box Series I-12)
    - National Committee to Abolish the House Un-American Activities Committee, 1964 (Box Series I-12)
    - O'Hara, Barratt (Congressional Record), 1965 (Box Series I-12)
    - Stamler, Jeremiah, 1965 (Box Series I-12)
    - Unidentified column, n. d. (Box Series I-12)
    - United States District Court for the Northern Division of Illinois, Eastern Division, 1965 (Box Series I-12)
      Stamler and Hall vs, Hon. Edwin E, Willis, et al
    - Wissler, Robert W. (Committee for Preserving Constitutional Rights), 1965 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hovanitz, William, 1944-53 (Box Series I-12)
  - Howard, Walter E., 1948-49 (Box Series I-12)
  - Howes, Paul G., 1921 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hsu, T.C., 1948 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hubbs, Carl L., 1938 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hudson, Paul, 1933 (Box Series I-12)
  - Huff, Clay G., 1957 (Box Series I-12)
  - Huggins, Charles, 1945 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hughes, James E., 1968 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hull, Fred H., 1935-51 (Box Series I-12)
  - Humphrey, Elliot S., 1924 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hunt, H.R., 1931-58 (Box Series I-12)
  - Hunter, C.K., 1922 (Box Series I-12)
  - Huntington, Ellsworth, 1945 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hunton, Peter, 1970 (Box Series I-13)
  - Huskins, C. Leonard, 1940-47 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hutt, F.B., 1932-51 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hutton, Thomas Hubert, 1919 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hyde, Roscoe R., 1921-24 (Box Series I-13)
  - Hyman, L., 1928 (Box Series I-13)
  - Ibsen, Heman L., 1933-42 (Box Series I-13)
  - Idrabo, J.M., 1968 (Box Series I-13)
  - Illinois Pacific Glass Company, 1931 (Box Series I-13)
  - Iltis, Hugh H., 1965 (Box Series I-13)
  - Ingle, Dwight J., 1959-63 (Box Series I-13)
  - Ingraham, M.H., 1935 (Box Series I-13)
  - Inhorn, S.L., 1980 (Box Series I-13)
  - Innes, Ernest, 1933 (Box Series I-13)
  - Innes, J.W., 1936 (Box Series I-13)
  - Institute of Genetic Biology-University of Chicago, 1932 (Box Series I-13)
    Lillie, Frank; Mason, Max
  - International Arts and Science Book Co., 1950 (Box Series I-13)
    Laub, Julius I.
  - International Commission on Eugenics, 1921 (Box Series I-13)
    Fairchild; Govaerts, Albert
  - International Conference on Population Genetics and Biology, 1974-75 (Box Series I-13)
    Karlin, Samuel; Nero, Eviator
  - International Exposition Chicago 1933-"A Century of Progress" (Box Series I-13)
    Pearson, Jay F.W.; Cromes, Carey
  - International Statistical Institute, 1947 (Box Series I-13)
    Rice, Stuart A.
  - Iowa State College Press, 1955 (Box Series I-13)
  - Ireneusz, Juvancz, 1958 (Box Series I-13)
  - Irwin, J.O., 1963 (Box Series I-13)
  - Irwin, M[alcolm] R[obert], 1937-51 (Box Series I-13)
  - Ives, Philip T., 1951 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jackson, Patricia, 1945 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jackson, R. Clay, 1920 (Box Series I-13)
  - The Jackson Laboratory Association of the Roscoe B. Jackson Memorial Laboratory, 1950 (Box Series I-13)
    Gantt, Robert
  - Jacobs, M.H., 1944 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jahn, Theodore L., 1956 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jain, Subodh K., 1962-67 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jameson, David L., 1970-77 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jameson, David L. and Marianne M., 1977 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jameson, Marianne M., 1977 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jay, George E. Jr., 1965 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jencks, Christopher, 1974 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jenkins, Alan, 1950 (Box Series I-13)
    Portrait of a Poet at College
  - Jenkins, John B., 1978 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jenkins, R.L., 1932 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jenks, A.E., 1944-45 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jensen, James W., 1949 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jensen, Louis, 1974 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jensen, N, P., 1920 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jensen, Paul, 1961 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jepson, G.L., 1947-49 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jest, Elizabeth L., 1921 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johanssen, Ivar, 1924 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johansson, 1963 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johns Hopkins Hospital, 1950-52 (Box Series I-13)
    Blalock, Alfred; Bard, Philip
  - Johnson, Michael S., 1978 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johnson, Roswell H., 1918-32 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johnson, Walter J. Inc., 1950 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johnson, Willis, 1959 (Box Series I-13)
  - Johnston, P.E., 1931 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jones, Champ M., 1952 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jones, Donald F., 1960 (Box Series I-13)
  - Jones, Harold E., 1927 (Box Series I-13)